That's what we're hoping to talk to you about here, Mr. President.
He's doing a good job. He was born for this job, I can tell you. Daniel, please.
Mr. President, thank you very much. I have two questions for you, if that's okay.
Seamus talked a little bit about the money aspect of this. Do you believe if you go after where the
money is coming from with Antifa, in regards to Antifa, do you believe that would be similar to
cutting the head off the snake, so to speak? It would help. I don't know that it would be
totally complete, but it would certainly knock out 75%, 80%, 85%. These people, a lot of them
don't believe it. I can almost tell a pro. They're like professionals. That's all they do.
And they get paid by somebody. I think it would knock out a lot of it. Yeah, not all of it,
maybe, but a lot of it. A lot of the people who we've listened
to over the last hour, they've emphasized that Antifa, it's not necessarily this big,
organized thing. It's a bit ambiguous. It's deorganized. I think that's one of the words
that Andy used. What is the challenges of going after a group that makes it intentionally
difficult to go after and find? That could be for you, the attorney general, anyone up there.
Well, they're smart people, and they deceive. A lot of them are crooked people. A lot of them
have been staying out of trouble their whole lives, and they've been bad from the day they
were born, frankly. But these are sick people. Pam, go ahead, please.
Well, they're smart, but they're not smart enough. Oh, my microphone's broken.
They're smart, but they're not smart enough. They have been covered by these liberal cities
for so many years, and that's why we're all working with Treasury,
with all these different departments, to find the criminal conspiracy.
Okay. I was just given a note by the Secretary of State saying that we're very close to a deal
in the Middle East, and they're going to need me pretty quickly, so we'll take a couple more
questions. Thank you, sir. I also have two questions for you, if I may. Have you given
any more thought to possibly suspending Ambious Corpus to not only deal with these insurrectionists
across the nation, but also to continue rapidly deporting illegal aliens? Yeah. Suspending who?